Guide to the Richard C. Jeffrey Papers, 1934-2002 ASP.2003.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Writings, Lectures, and Publications, 1952-2002; IV.
  This series is divided into three subseries consisting of manuscript drafts, lecture notes and conferences, and editorial work. The manuscript drafts feature Jeffrey's writings at various stages of their development, ranging from early outlines to pre-publication galley proofs. The second subseries mainly comprises lecture notes and transparencies used in presentations. The third subseries holds material produced during Jeffrey's editorial role in publishing Hempel's Selected Philosophical Essays.
  - Manuscript Drafts, 1952-2002; 1.
    This subseries features Jeffrey's manuscripts, which often include communications and comments by others since Jeffrey often shared his writings to seek critical review and feedback.
    The folders are arranged chronologically, followed by undated material, which is arranged alphabetically according to title.
    - "On the Explication of Causal Conditionals", Master Thesis, University of Chicago, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - "Epistemology Without the Given: A Study in Radical Physicalism", PhD Thesis, 1st Draft, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - "Contributions to the Theory of Inductive Probability", PhD Thesis, w/ Carnap Correspondence, Princeton, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - "On Changing One's Betting Function: Probability Kinematics", 1958 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - "Automata: Finite Recursion, Computer Logic, et al.", 1958-1961 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - "Some Recent Simplifications of the Theory of Finite Automata", MIT Technical Report, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - "On the Paradox of Ideal Evidence", (Popper), 1959 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - "Betting, Learning, and Confirming Generalizations", 1960 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "De Finetti's Representation Theorem", Second Draft, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - "Studies in Inductive Logic & Probability Vol. II", Correspondence & Notes, 1960-1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - "Toward a Unified Theory of Probability and Desirability", 1962 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - "Counterfactuals as Explanations", 1963 and undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - "Preference Between Propositions (Short)", Stanford University, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Writings on Random Propositions, 1963-1971 and undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - "Preference-Preserving Utility Transformations" and Corrections, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - "Preference, Credence, and Utility", Various Drafts, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - "Preference, Credence, and Utility", Various Drafts, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "Mises Redux", and Writings by Others on 'Randomness,', 1966-1974 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - "The Logic of Decision": Reviews & Correspondence, 1966-1990 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - "Notes on the Logic of Decision", 1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - "Bride of Udolpho Meets Button Man", (Popper), 1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - "Interpersonal Comparison of Utilities/Preferences", 1968 and undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - "Two Practical Paradoxes", "Antithetic of Practical Reason?" and The Prisoner's Dilemma", 1968 and undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - "Causality in the Logic of Decision", and "Preference & Causality", 1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Harsanyi on Utility Summation, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - "The New Utilitarianism", Various Drafts, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - "Event-Valued Random Variables = Propositional Functions of Possible Worlds", 1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Notes on Decision Theory, 1971 and undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - "Remarks on Interpersonal Utility Theory", 1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Utilitarianism Revisited (Larger Version of APA Symposium Paper), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - "Studies in Inductive Logic", Vol. 2, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - "The Logic of Decision", 2nd Edition, 1971-1989 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - "The Logic of Decision", 2nd Edition, 1971-1989 (Box 14, Folder 11 B)
    - "Preference and Modality", 1st Draft, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Review by Jeffrey of "On the Coherence of Higher-Order Probabilities" by Soshichi Uchii, 1974 and undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Review by Jeffrey of "On the Coherence of Higher-Order Probabilities" by Soshichi Uchii, 1974 and undated (Box 14, Folder 13 B)
    - "David Says", 1975 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - "State Bayesianism", Chelsea College, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - "Harsanyi's Theorem", 1975-1984 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - "On Inductive Logic", 1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - "Axiomatizing the Logic of Decision", 1976 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - "Savage's Omelet", 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - "Savage's Omelet", 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 19 B)
    - "Conditionals as Proposition-Valued Functions of Possible Worlds", 1977 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - "Introductory Logic: Notes and Problems", 1978 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - "Skyrms on Probability Kinematics via Second-Order Probabilities", 1978 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - "Why Look Before You Leap?" 1978 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - "Choice, Chance, & Credence", Draft and Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Formal Logic: Its Scope and Limits, 3rd Edition, 1978-1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Formal Logic: Its Scope and Limits, 3rd Edition, 1978-1988 (Box 15, Folder 1 B)
    - Formal Logic: Its Scope and Limits, 3rd Edition, 1978-1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - "Cohen's Nativism", 1981 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - "Ratifiability (Corrected)", 1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - "Preference and Choiceworthiness", 1981 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - "Bayesianism with a Human Face", 1982-1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - "Bayesianism with a Human Face", 1982-1990 (Box 15, Folder 6 B)
    - "The Sure Thing Principle", (Philosophy of Science Association): Drafts, Notes, Readings, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - "The Sure Thing Principle", (Philosophy of Science Association): Drafts, Notes, Readings, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 7 B)
    - "The Impossibility of Inductive Probability", Letters to the Editor of Nature by Jeffrey, Levi, Good, Popper et al, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - "Probability and the Logic of Confirmation", Paper in Honor of Carl G. Hempel's Retirement from Univ. of Pittsburgh, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - "Indefinite Probability Judgment: A Reply to Levi", Drafts and Correspondence, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - "Indefinite Probability Judgment: A Reply to Levi", Drafts and Correspondence, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 10 B)
    - "Probabilism and Induction", 1986 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - "Probability and the Art of Judgment", 1986 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - "Biting the Bayesian Bullet: Zeckhauser's Problem", 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - "Biting the Bayesian Bullet: Zeckhauser's Problem", 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 13 B)
    - "How to Probabilize a Newcomb Problem", 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - "De Finetti's Radical Probabilism", 1988 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - "Conditionals", 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - "Thrilled by the Facts", Article on F.P. Ramsey for the Times Literary Supplement, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - "UCLA: The Experiential Element in Knowledge", 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - "Chance Kinematics", 1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - "The Kinematics of Preferential Choice", 1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - "Newcomb Kinematics", 1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - "Probability Kinematics and Causality", 1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - "A Skeleton Key to JM Joyce's Axtiomatic Foundations of Bayesian Decision Theory, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Formal Logic: Its Scope & Limits: Reviews, Comments, and Revisions for 4th Edition, 1992-1997 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - "Causality in the Logic of Decision (Castiglioncello)", 1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - "Causality in the Logic of Decision", 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - "Judgemental Probability Dynamics: Formation, Transformation, Reparation", 1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Preference Kinematics, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - "Probability Reparation: The Problem of New Explanation", 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - "Hempel", Entry for Routledge Encyclopedia of Philosophy, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - "Probabilistic Thinking", with E-mail to Peter Momtchiloff, 1993-2002 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - "Probabilistic Thinking", 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - "Son of Born: Judgemental Probabilities in Quantum Mechanics", 1994 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - "Bayes Ways: A Probability Primer", 1995 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Jeffrey's Review of "A Vindication of Probabilistic Foundationalism", by Unknown Author for Philosophical Studies, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Formal Logic: Its Scope and Limits, Revisions for 4th Edition, 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - "Transformations of Belief", Drafts, 1995-1999 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - "Probabilistic Epistemology", 1995-2000 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - "The Dreaded Problem of New Explanation, a.k.a Old Evidence" (Chapter 5), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - "Logicism 2000: A Mini-Manifesto", 1996 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - "What it Takes to be a Group: Pareto vs. Diversity", w/ Matthias Hild and Mathias Risse, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - "An Appreciation of Richard Bradley's Decision Theory with Conditionals, 1998 (Fragment) (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - "Aumann's 'No Agreement' Theorem Generalized", 1998 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - "Bumblebee Attitudes", 1998 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - "Neo-Bayesian Reflections on 'Nature Is Only There Once,' and Other Neo-Positivist Slogans", 1998 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - "Problems of Preference Aggregation", together w/ Matthias Hild and Mathias Risse, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - "Bumblebee Attitudes", 1999 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - "Decision-Theoretic Aggregation'Introduction and Survey", 1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - "Probabilistic Judgement", 1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - "Personal Probabilities for Quantum Mechanics", (Ischia), 1999-2001 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - "Some Solved Problems of Probabilism", 2000 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - "Epistemology Probabilized", 2001 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Subjective Probability: The Real Thing", 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - "Flipping and Ex post Aggregation", with Mathias Hild and Mathias Risse, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - "Logicism Lite", incl. correspondence with Penelope Maddy, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - "Logicism Lite", incl. correspondence with Penelope Maddy, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 11 B)
    - "Noncoöperative Games & Individual Decisions", 2002 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - "Probabilism & Induction", (Chapter 5), 2002 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - "2nd Order Logic Unformizable" (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - "Allais's Qualms About Expected Utility" (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - "Barycentric Probability Display Program" (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - "Bernoullian Utility: The St. Petersburg Paradox", (Chapter 2) (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - "Bridgman's Operational Analysis" (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - "Carnap's Minisystems of 'Logical Probability'" (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - "Carnap's 'Model A' System of Inductive Logic, Based on c*" (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - "Choice and Preference" (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - "Choosing", Draft of Chapter 6 of Subjective Probability: The Real Thing. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - "Comparative Probability" (Chapter 5) (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - "Conditioning", Draft of Chapter 3, Subjective Probability: The Real Thing. (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - "Constructivism After Carnap: Project Description" (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - "The Covering Law Model of Explanation" (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - "Decision-Making", (Chapter 6) (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - "Decision Theory and Human Action" (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - "Decision Theory Notes (Penn)" (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - "De Finetti's Account of Subjective Probability: Two Versions" (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - "Dopo Carnap": Italian Translation of Jeffrey's "After Carnap" (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - "Epistemology Without the Given: A Study in Radical Physicalism" (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - "Expectation Primer", Draft of Chapter 4, Subjective Probability: The Real Thing. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - "If", City College of New York (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - "Interpersonal Comparison of Utilities", ("Distributive Justice as a Problem for Utilitarianism") (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - "The Kinematics of Decision" (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - "The Limits of Formal Methods (Part Three)" (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - "The Logic of Decision" (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - "The Logic of Decision Revised" (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - "The Logic of Preference" (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - "Logical Positivism", Encyclopedia Entry (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - "Notes on the Theory of Automata", (City College of New York) (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - "An Objectivist's Guide to Subjective Chance" (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - "Physicalism without the Given", Notes and Drafts (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - "Plato: The Third Man", Revised Edition, for Prof. Ackrill's Seminar (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - "Postcript: How to Think" (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - "Preference & Choiceworthiness (Chapter 12) (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - "Probabilities of Acts: Defense of a Unified Ontology for Decision Theory" (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - "Probability Dynamics and Causality" (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - "Probability Dynamics; Collaboration", Draft of Chapter 3, Subjective Probability: The Real Thing. (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - "Probability, Induction, and Decision Theory", Section 7&8 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - "Probability Logic", Chapter 2 (Summary) (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - "Probabilizing" (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - "Proposition-Valued Random Variables: A Progress Report" (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - "Random Propositions" (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - "Ratificationism Reconsidered" (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Review of Van McGee's "Conditional Probabilities and Compounds of Conditionals" (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Review of Frank Plympton Ramsey: Notes on Philosophy, Probability, and Mathematics by Maria Carla Galavotti (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - "Rough Probabilism" (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - "Second-Order Logic Unformalizable" (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - "Self-Reference" (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "Smokers' Dilemmas" (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - "Son of Savage: Consequences as Propositions", and "Ramsey, Son of Savage" (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - "Subjective Frequentism" (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - "Subjective Probability, The Real Thing: Decision", (Chapter 7) (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - "Take Back the Day! Jon Dorling's Bayesian Solution of the Duhem Problem" (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - "Toward a Reformulation of Ramsey's Theory of Preference" (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - "Unknown Probabilities" (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - "Updating on Statistics", Draft of Chapter 5, Subjective Probability: The Real Thing. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - "Von Neumann-Morgenstern Utility Theory" (Chapter 3) and "Comparative Probability" (Chapter 5) (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - "What is Probability?" and "Note on Unique Decipherability", by E.T. Jaynes (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - "Wrapping It Up" (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Annotated Published Writings by Jeffrey (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Lecture Notes and Conferences, 1964-2001; 2.
    The majority of the material consists of Jeffrey's lecture notes and transparencies. Some folders also contain material relating to his conference preparations and attendance such as correspondence, programs, abstracts, and travel arrangements.
    The folders are arranged chronologically, followed by undated material, which is arranged alphabetically according to lecture title or conference name.
    - "If", APA Meeting, Boston, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - International Congress for Logic, Methodology, and Philosophy of Science, Jerusalem: Program and Abstracts, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - "The Prisoner's Dilemma", Princeton University, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - International Congress of Logic, Methodology, and Philosophy of Science, London, Ontario, Canada, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - "Subjective Probability": Talk for Statistics Seminar, London University, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - "Coming True", Lecture for Conference on the Philosophy of Language & Logic, University of Warwick, March 1976 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - IV Simposio Latino-Americano de Logica Matematica (IV SLAM): Motion for Withdrawal ASL Sponsorship, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - 7th International Congress of Logic, Methodology, and Philosophy of Science, Salzburg, Austria 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - International Conference on the Foundations of Probability & Statistics, Luino, Italy, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - "Carnap on Artificial Languages and Artificial Lives", Boston Colloquium for the Philosophy of Science and "Carnap's Robots", Center for the Philosophy of Science, Pittsburgh, 1982-1985 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - "Judgmental Probability and Objective Chance", Siena Conference, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Conference on "Exchangeability and Partial Exchangeability", Purdue University, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - "From Logical Probability to Probability Logic", Bar-Hillel Symposium, Boston University, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - "Probability & Induction", 1985 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - "Alias Smith and Jones: The Testimony of the Senses", Essler Conference, Frankfurt, May 1986, 1885-1987 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Juror Decision Making Conference, Northwestern University, Evanston, Illinois, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Frankfurt and Bologna Lectures, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Princeton Colloquium Speakers, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Lecture Programs and Announcements, Italy, 1986-1993 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - "Probabilistic Epistemology: De Finetti's 'Probabilismo' (1931)", Moscow, Aug., 1987 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - "Conditionals", Dunwalke Conference, Lecture Draft and Transparencies, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Joint US-Italian Workshop on Knowledge, Belief, and Strategic Interaction, Castiglioncello Italy, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Salamanca Conference "Ciencia y Conocimiento", Spain, Programs and Correspondence, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Lectures in Genova and Turin, Italy, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - 8th International Congress of Logic, Methodology, & Philosophy of Science, Florence, August 1995, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - "Decision Kinematics", IEA Conference on Rationality in Economics, Turin, and Revised, 1993-1996 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Luino III & Trieste Conferences 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - IEA Turin Conference: The Rational Foundations of Economic Behaviour, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - International Conference: The Notion of Event in Probabilistic Epistemology, Trieste, Italy, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - "What It Takes to be a Group: Pareto vs. Diversity", Caen, France, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - "I Was a Teenage Logical Positivist (Now a Septuagenarian Radical Probabilist)", PSA Presidential Address 1998, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - "The Career of Logical Empiricism", History of Science Society, Pittsburgh, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Probabilistic States of Mind: IPMU 8th International Conference on Information Processing and Management of Uncertainty in Knowledge Based Systems, Madrid 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - "After Logical Empiricism", 2000 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - "I. After Logical Empiricism, II. Radical Probabilism", Petrus Hispanus Lectures, Lisbon, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - "Empiricism Probabilized", Theoretical Aspects of Rationality and Knowledge (TARK) Lecture, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - "From Logical Empiricism to Radical Probabilism", Program and Abstract for Hägerström Lecture, Uppsala University, Schweden, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - "Joyce on Choice" & Reply by Jim Joyce, Central Division APA Meeting, Minneapolis, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - "Judgmental Probabilities, Conditional and Unconditional", ISBA, Laguna Beach, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - "Probabilistic Epistemology--or--Après épistémologie", Carnegie Mellon University, 05-25-02, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Carnegie Mellon University Talks "Probability Dynamics" and "Logicism Lite", Lecture Notes and Correspondence, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - "Adoptive (Constructive) Probability", et al., Transparencies, Rome (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - "After Logicism", Transparancies (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - "Agreeing to Disagree: Harsanyi & Aumann", w/ Matthias Hild & Mathias Risse, Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - "Conditional Probability", Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - "Epistemology Re-Naturalized", Transparancies (Bees) (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - "Evolutionary Decision Theory", SF Talk (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - "Exchangeability & Generalized Conditioning", & "Mini-Aumann Theorem", Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - "Fallacies re. Radical Probabilism", Transparencies for Bologna/Lisbon Lectures (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - "Irrationality and the Bayesian Enlightenment", Announcement of Lecture at the University of Bristol (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - "Jon Dorling's Solution of the Duhem-Quine Problem", Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - "Judgemental Probability", Jerusalem, Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - "Logical Probability (Objective Bayesianism)", Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - "Probabilistic Epistemology", Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - "Probabilities of Preference Aggregation", Cal Tech Talk, Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - "Probability Dynamics and Causality", Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - "Probability Kinematics", Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - "Prospects for Pure Pragmatism", Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - "Radical Probabilism, et al.", Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - "Savage on the Cheap", Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - "The Theory of Knowledge", First Lecture (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - "What It Takes to be a Group: Pareto vs. Diversity", Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Unidentified Lecture Notes and Transparencies (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Editorial Work: Hempel's Selected Philosophical Essays, 1934-2000; 3.
    Jeffrey functioned as the editor of Hempel's Selected Philosophical Essays. Gathered here are documents produced during this process, mostly in form of different production stages of the publication and copies of Hempel's essays considered for publication.
    This subseries is divided into three sections. Sections 1 and 2 group material according to the format of the publication: Preprint Versions and Galley Proofs. The third section comprises the remaining material related to the editorial process.
    Section: Preprint Versions
    - Pre-print versions
      - Chapters 4, 8, 13, 15,19,20, 22, 23, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 15, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Chapters 10, 14, 21, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Chapters 10, 17,19, 21, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Chapters 11, 12, 15, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 11 and English Translation of Hempel's PhD Thesis, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 23 and Copies of Hempel's Writings, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Chapter 1, Copies of Hempel's Writings, and Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Chapter 6 and English Translation of Hempel's PhD Thesis, 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Chapters 9, 11, 12, 14, 16 and Notes and Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Chapters 8, 9, 12, English Translation of Hempel's PhD Thesis, and Copies of Hempel's Writings, 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Introduction and Related Transparencies, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Chapters 1, 5, 13, and Copies of Hempel's Writings, 1996-1999 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Chapters 1-16, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Chapters 1-16 and Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Chapters 1-6, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Chapters 7-11, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Chapters 12-15, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Galley Proofs